Hello friends, I welcome you to your own
YouTube channel.
Today we are going to
talk about ICICI Lombard stock. For the past
few days, there has been some very good
news coming in, but the price movement is
not reflecting the results of that news. So,
I received a lot of subscribe
requests, Sir,
how can we see ICICI Lombard?
Today, we will discuss the details about it on
both technical and fundamental
basis. So, friends, let's
start with the ICICI
Lombard share price.
Before we proceed further, please cut this tomato.
This is very important. So,
friends, we have come to discuss the
technical aspects of ICICI Lombard stock. I have taken a
day recharge here. But as
you all know, before investing in any stock, it is very important that
its fundamentals are good along with a profit. So,
therefore, we will do the
fundamentals before the technicals. For that,
we will go to the skin and die in that. So,
friends, we are here.  This spinner is
on the team and the
fundamentals of ICICI Lombard share are
open in front of us, here if I look at the book value, then
Ali is back at 171 in that bathroom
and the current market price is
1628, that means if I calculate the
current market price Gullu Cardio here, then
that rescue
comes around 19.50 which is considered to be quite expensive,
but friends, if I look at the
tribal of ICICI Lombard share here, then
it is much above 26.98 25,
so I can get a cylinder in it, that means
its profitability from spider-man is
accident and along with this, if
I look at the accused, that is also 21.78 center, then
this is also almost one and a half times of fifteen, so I can
call this also match select and
friends, if I keep the face value, then
this stop has never been split off, so
its growth in the coming time, the
ability to give bonus, the
ability to split, is Akbar, so
I am positive on this  I can consider this point and along with this,
this stock also
provides dividend from time to time to its
shareholders, leaving aside the price PM here and
this is the top, if I
look at the stock here, then it is 60.4 which is
quite high above the earth, so this is a little bit better,
but friends, here I am sad about the
tribal and accused of ICICI Lombard share
and when the face value is visible,
according to this I can take the stock price and those who are
willing to convert, both of these
in justification, so friends,
here we are
getting the basic fundamental of ICICI Lombard share,
according to that the stock price is a bit
expensive, but in the long term it can have the
potential to go even higher, so that is why
I can
give positive marking to this fundamental,
but friends, we will do a little more
detail about it and for that we will
go to its profit and loss treatment,
so friends, here we have come to the
profit and loss treatment of ICICI Lombard share
and I or the car  If I
start looking from 2018,
you will see an increase in both sales and operating profit on a yearly and near term basis.
This is 20%. After this, see, there
is an increment here. Leave aside Paytm, this is
estimated further. Whatever is there till March 21,
you can see that the
yearly and investment has increased here, which is
considered a very positive point, friends,
because it is on a growth stand. In the same
way, if you look at the GPS here, then
in this piece also you will
see an increase on a yearly basis, friends,
this is also a positive point. So, on the profit and
loss treatment, we did
not see any negative thing even in the short term,
but friends, here we are
also an indicator of the long term, so for the long term,
we will check its balance sheet this time. So,
we have come to the
balance sheet of ICICI Lombard share. If I
see the result here, then
show me the intimate here at 19020.  This is a very positive point and
if I look at it, the gas reserve for voice mail is
less than three percent, which
means it is currently hovering around five percent
and if I look at the last few years,
its bonus is also in a stable position, whereas the
SAFE is not increasing, there is no increase here
but there is no increase either, so
I can consider this as a neutral point
and this company is an
insurance company, so friends,
I do not need acid because friends,
as you all know that the
maximum insurance company has
started insurance business online, so
its office is big or the insurance
companies do
not have a factory, so please, this does
not hold that much importance for us, for Tuesday
ICICI Lombard share, we
will ignore the acid and friends,
before going into the technical chart, I
want to show you two news which can have a
huge impact on the price of this share, the
first news which came a few days ago, you
can see it here, only courage, this is
from Bharti AXA General Insurance  ICICI
Lombard Completed means Bharti AXA General
Insurance has sold a part of its business
to ICICI Lombard.
This means that friends, the customer base of ICICI Lombard is going to
grow even more,
its business is going to grow even more, this
growth is not shown to you in this year's Devar Fundamentals
page, but next
year we are going to see its effect on a large side
and along with this,
friends, I will also show you another one, the
use of the second one is ICR Dad Science
Painless Table Rating ₹2.250 million sa body
dated ICICI Lombard. Friends, this
news is also
based on that, that is, even after the disaster that happened with Bharti AXA General Insurance,
ICICI CID mentioned it and
gave it a tree yellow meaning steel railing, so
friends, this too
can show a lot of atoms to people on it in the coming time,
so friends, according to the total fundamentals, the long term performance of
ICICI Lombard share
Limit your long term outlook is visible to us,
it is also looking positive, so
here we can think of investing in both long term and short term
ways, so
friends, let us
go to the ICICI Lombard chart
and see
where we can create a position if we want to do so, so
friends, we have come
to the technical chart of ICICI Lombard share and
I have taken day recharge here and
in this chart, I draw all my lines,
so you can see this chart
which I will try to explain to you completely now
and will try to tell you
how you
can enter in it, so as friends, you
can see that since the ICICI Lombard note was
published in the news in September, the
price has not moved much, which
means friends, we still have a
good offer here and if I
look at the price from before that, then the
price is stuck inside a channel from
there and this channel has neither looked upwards
nor downwards.  There is a lot of news, and
friends, if the news is positive, then it seems
a little difficult to be quiet on the downside right now.
And the behavior that is visible is of a
bookish movement upwards because
every time the price tries to go up,
you will see the volume record here.
Look, here we will see a
green candle with more or higher volume at one place,
this means that its trend is
still upwards. Even though you have
not been given a bank account here yet, but please
give it to the side very soon.
Friends, if I talk about position taking, then
here I have given two levels, one is the
blackout level which is of the level 165
5.00, meaning 1604 500 and the second one is a
bounce level, meaning its value is
1470. We can take our position anywhere between these two levels,
but there will be
some method for it. Thanks. If this background
level is already broken here and it
breaks with high volume, then we can take
our position at the breakout level, meaning 1655,
because as I said  If the news
is positive, then the chances of a comeback are the
highest. But friends, the
breakout should be on high volume,
which is our fabric, so we will
not take a position there. And the second thing is that it is
possible that the price may come down even further
and here, try to establish support on the channel line of this channel.
If I see it going up while forming support on the Loot Channel, then
we can buy it here around the Loot Channel, which
means
we can also create a position around 1470. And if it
makes a good bundle here, then
next it may black out and go up.
And as we are
thinking of long term investment here, then I will keep the
target open here.
In Kundan, it may go very high. Which
means we
can also double-triple the money side, but if someone
wants to book a partial profit, then do it at 90. You
can book it here because the
meter has edited 90 from the moon, it is
about eight.  If it is percent then if someone wants to
book part profit or book it in meter then the
level of 90 can be a
very good level for that so
friends I hope you understood this video
if you liked this video
and got to learn something from this video then
like this video on YouTube
subscribe to the channel and press the bell icon
so that the notification of the next video
reaches you first and if
you need any guidance in the live market
then you can turn on our Telegram channels
and there you can post your questions on the discussion board,
this should be done, it does
not cost any money, you will get the link of the Telegram channel
both below this video and in the description so friends that's all for today
in this video, turn
on the next education hub